本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： VK  Era  大力  卢尔摩斯  红鼻子的UFO  YU  熊猫大虾
校对/后期： iamazed
深影字幕组微博 weibo.com/syfansub
机器之心
第一季  第三集
这是2048年
The year is 2048.
不断发展的科技渐渐不受管束
Evolving technologies can no longer be regulated.
危险的高新技术永久地改变了犯罪的领域
Dangerous advancements forever alter the criminal landscape.
警察措手不及
Police are not prepared.
为与这种罪恶抗争 执法机关采用了新型防御武器
Law enforcement combats this corruption with a new line of defense.
但这些武器并不全然相同
But not all are created equal.
DRN的设计初衷是让其尽可能的和人类接近
The idea behind the DRNs was to be as human as possible.
他们是基于一个叫人造灵魂的项目而开发
They were based on a program called Synthetic Soul.
这是疯了的那款吧
That's one of the crazy ones.
- 我带你去 - 我们走
- I'll lead you in? - Let's go.
现在所有的警察
Now all cops...
人类联手人造人一起战斗 保护人民
human and manmade together... take on the battle to watch over us all.
充电已完成
Charge at capacity.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 詹姆斯
Hey, James.
- 早上好 纳瓦罗先生 - 你好吗
- Morning, Mr. Navarro. - How you doing?
米勒小姐
Miss Miller.
哦 詹姆斯
Oh. James.
你又忘记把钥匙从锁上取下来了
Left your key in the lock again.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我发誓我的记忆力一天比一天糟
I swear my memory gets worse every day.
我告诉过你 如果你想的话
I told you, I can have maintenance come in
我可以让维修工过来 把它们都换成生物锁
and switch those out for bio locks if you'd like.
没关系啦 我还是喜欢传统方式
That's all right, I prefer the old-fashioned way.
- 我一定很可笑吧 - 没 我挺喜欢的
- I'm funny, I guess. - No, no, no, I like that.
这个送到了安检台 是给你的
Uh, this came to the security desk for you.
哦 谢谢你
Oh, thank you.
我得回到岗位上去了
I got to get back to the desk.
再见
See you.
你好 需要帮忙吗
Hi, can I help you?
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
詹姆斯
James.
我们走
Let's go.
服务器机房
你知道我最喜欢你的哪方面吗
You know what I love best about you?
你的守时
Your punctuality.
你这是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
你迟到了
You're late
而且这车一股橄榄油味儿
and the car smells like olive oil.
拿着这个
Hold this...
还有这个
and this.
我在做些什么
What am I doing here?
帮我热咖啡
You're heating my coffee.
嘿
Hey!
我喜欢喝热的
I like it hot.
咖啡的最佳饮用温度在68到80摄氏度
It's best between 155 and 175 degrees.
大多数人喜欢喝80度的
Most people prefer it at 175.
你喜欢74度的 它现在就是这个温度
You like it at 165, and that's what it is.
你连我喜欢喝怎样的咖啡都知道
You know how I like my coffee?
对 我不像你 我注意细节
Yes, I, unlike you, pay attention to details,
比如现在几点了
like what time it is
还有你几点该接你的搭档一起去换班
and what time you're supposed to pick up your partner for shift.
我也注意细节的
Oh, I pay attention to details,
比如你刚刚把手指伸进了我的咖啡
like you just put your finger in my coffee.
如果你喜欢的话 我可以把它伸到别的地方去
If you'd like, I could put it somewhere else.
等等等等 回去
Wa-Wa-Wait, go back.
- 回到哪去 - 回到我没有搭档的时候
- To where? - To when I didn't have a partner
我可以安静地开车去上班
and I could drive to work in peace.
我知道你听从我的建议
I know you took my advice
在你的腿上涂了橄榄油 约翰
and used olive oil on your leg, John,
确实有效
and it works.
你只是太固执了
You're just too stubborn
不会说谢谢 但是不用客气
to say thank you, but you're welcome.
我吃了份沙拉 一份希腊沙拉
I ate a salad... a Greek salad.
希腊沙拉中会添加橄榄油
早上八点就吃
At 10:00 a.m.?
天啊 你可真是当侦探的料
Boy, you're some detective.
真不容易 这才对嘛
Finally. Now you're talking.
接到报案 凶杀案
13 RAY. Possible 31.
似乎还在进行中
Homicide.
在新月街4500号发现尸体
Body discovered at 4500 Crescent Av.
离这三个街区
That's three blocks away.
好啦 我们去工作吧
All right, let's go to work.
你们在这里多久了
How long you been here?
我们也刚到
We just got here.
枪击时没有目击者
There were no witnesses to the shooting.
案件发生在过去的二十分钟内
The incident happened within the last 20 minutes.
谁发现的他
Who found him?
这两个人
These two,
我们已经封锁了这片区域
and we've cordoned off the area.
他们毁掉了摄像头
They killed the cameras.
我想我应该可以读取到已存档的录像
I think I can still access the archived footage.
约翰
John...
他们去了二十五层
They went up to the 25th floor.
他们关闭了电梯
They shut down the elevator.
把安保录像传送给马尔多纳多
Transmit that security footage to Maldonado,
我们也许能查到这些家伙的身份
so we can try and I.D. these guys.
哈里森警官 去请求支援
Officer Harrison, call for backup
并执行疏散方案
and begin evacuation protocols.
遵命
Yes, sir.
注意安全 嫌疑犯仍在这所建筑物中
And be careful. Perps are still in the building.
没问题
You got it.
计划是什么
What's the plan?
我也不知道
I got no idea...
但是我们有二十五层楼的时间想出来
but we got 25 floors to figure it out.
交出手机
Hand over the phone.
闭嘴
Shut your mouth.
交出来
Hand it over.
不要说话
Stop talking.
让我看见它 嘿
Let me see it... hey, hey.
我说了
I told you,
坐下
you sit down.
你好
Hello.
你叫什么
What's your name?
你不知道该怎么回答 是吗
Oh, you, you don't know how to answer that, do you?
你担心如果你回答了 你会受伤 是吧
You're afraid if you answer, you'll get hurt, huh?
可是唯一能避免受伤的方法
Well... the only way around that is...
就是你如实回答
that you answer honestly.
这总是最佳对策
It's always the best policy.
詹娜
Jenna.
你为何不来加入我呢 詹娜
Why don't you come and join me, Jenna?
喂
Yo.
我们可以开始了
We can start now.
警察还在大厅里
Cops are still in the lobby.
那就是他们的错了
Well, that's their fault.
是时候让他们注意到我们了
It's time to get their attention.
闪开 闪开
Out of the way, out of the way.
蹲下
Stay down.
警察 继续走
Police. Keep moving.
这不是演习
This is not a drill.
- 怎么回事 - 先生 请您继续走
- What's going on? - Sir, we need you to keep moving,
直到走出大楼
continuing out of the building.
- 下楼梯 - 外面怎么了
- Go down the stairwell. - What's going on out there?
- 请出去 - 今天不用上班了
- Out of the building, please. - Take the rest of the day off.
去楼梯那里 从大楼后门出去
Move to the stairs, exit the back of the building.
现在什么情况 斯特尔
What's the update, Stahl?
市中心的桑德森大楼出事了
It's the Sanderson building downtown.
约翰正在爬楼梯 目前在第二层
John's on the second floor ascending.
爬楼梯
Ascending?
约翰
John!
你那什么情况
What's your status?
多利安说大楼结构还是安全的
Dorian says the building is still structurally sound.
第三和第四层的紧急出口被破坏了
There's damage to the third and fourth emergency exits.
东南角的楼梯也被堵住了
The southeast stairwell is also blocked.
紧急救援人员正在把人们从第二层撤离
Emergency personnel are getting people out by the second story.
约翰 别爬楼梯了
John, do not ascend.
我不允许
Negative.
继续把员工引导至二层 然后你也待在那儿
Continue to direct the employees to the second floor and go there yourself
直到我们弄清对手是谁
until we know what we're dealing with here.
我知道对手是谁
I know what we're dealing with.
攻击者还在楼内
The assailants are still in the building.
我们去追他
We're going after them.
给我点时间
Buy me some time.
你应该启动装置
You should initiate the protocol.
阻断所有进出大楼的信号
Jam all comm signals coming in and out of the building,
切断他们的通讯
cut their communication,
再给我找些后援
and get me some backup.
约翰 如果我们阻断信号 通讯信号就传不出大楼
John, if we jam the signal, comms won't make it out of the building.
我们就无法联系了
We won't be able to communicate.
请你立刻离开大楼
Leave the building now.
这... 我不...
There's... I can't...
啥... 做...
What... do...
是否...
Do you...
圣诞
Christmas.
你竟然挂断了马尔多纳多队长的电话
Did you just hang up on Captain Maldonado?
反正她总说那些无聊的话
Yeah, boring conversation anyway.
我就喜欢你这态度 不服从命令 还理直气壮
I just love that you wear your insubordination like it's a virtue.
人们都撤出区域了吗
Did we evacuate the perimeter?
按照疏散方案 三个街区都已清空
Per protocol, three-block radius.
我是保罗
Yeah, this is Paul.
截断一切通讯
Lock down communications.
启动通讯封堵
Initiate the jam.
启动序列
Sequence initiated.
好的 信号已激活
Okay, signal active.
转换至内部通讯
Switching to internal comms.
他们堵了通信
They jammed us.
所有外部通信通道都断了
All external communications are blocked.
预测执法者的举动真是容易
Law enforcement is nothing if not predictable.
A队 盯住南边
Alpha team, take the north side.
B队 盯住屋顶
Bravo team, take the rooftop.
没有命令不要开枪
Hold your fire until instructed.
安全
Clear.
那个计划有什么进展没
Any more thoughts on that plan?
我们都快到了 约翰
We're running out of floors, John.
我以为这会儿后援就到了
Well, I thought backup would be here by now.
看来只能继续往上了
Guess we just keep moving up.
也许还有别的方法
Maybe there's another option.
这里的通风系统是相通的
The entire air system is interconnected.
我们只需要到二十三层
We just have to make it to the 23rd floor.
二十三层有个通风口 能把我们带到那帮人那儿
There's an access door to the air system there that'll take us up to where these guys are.
看吧 都说了我们会想到办法的
See? Told you we'd come up with a plan.
嘿
Hey.
你脸上怎么有迪斯科花纹
What's with the disco face?
你想说什么
Got something to tell me?
因为通讯被堵住了
Since the signals are now being jammed,
这栋楼里所有的紧急电话都打出不去
every emergency call being placed in this building is bouncing back to me
所以都转给了我
because they can't get out.
接电话 也许我们能知道一些信息
Answer the calls. We might get some information.
你好
Hello?
谢天谢地 我需要警察帮助 我在办公室里 刚才发生了爆炸
别着急女士 我知道了 警察正在赶来的路上
请您先移步至二楼
你这是搞什么
What are you doing?
在葡萄牙文化中
In the Portuguese culture,
已经证明女性的声音在危机时刻
it is proven that people find a woman's voice more soothing
更能舒缓情绪
in moments of crisis.
- 你好 - 你好
- Hello? - Hello.
我是约翰・肯尼思探长
I'm Detective John Kennex.
我是个性格怪异的电子警察
I'm an automated police officer with a very difficult personality.
是911吗
911?
请保持冷静
Please remain calm.
我...我这里有一个枪手
I'm... I'm trapped with a gunman.
请帮帮我
Please help.
没事的 请深呼吸
Everything's all right. Just take a breath.
你叫什么名字
What is your name?
我叫佩吉
It's Paige.
你好 佩吉
Hi, Paige.
你能跟我们说说这枪手吗
What can you tell me about the gunmen?
我不知道
I don't know.
我妹妹在他们手上
They have my sister...
还有其他人
and others.
听着 佩吉
Listen, Paige,
我现在就在这栋大厦里
I'm in the building.
你要回答我几个问题
I need to ask you a few questions,
但首先我要知道的是 你现在安全吗
but first I need to know... are you safe?
你现在没有被劫持是吗
Are you out of harm's way?
我想是的
I think so.
- 目前为止 - 很好 听我说
- For now. - Okay, listen to me.
你现在在哪 你在第几层
Where are you? What floor are you on?
我在二十五层
I'm on the 25th floor.
我藏在储藏室里
I'm in the utility closet.
接下来
Next face.
你 跪下
You, on your knees.
跪下
On your knees!
不 不 不要
Oh, no, no!
噢 天呐
Oh, God.
佩吉
Paige?
佩吉 发生什么事了
Paige, what's happening?
他们杀了他
They've shot him.
卢死了
Lou is dead.
嘿 小兵 给我拿点水
Hey, dogface. Water.
是一具尸体
We got a body!
条子滚开
不要让人群接近
Keep those people back!
那些混蛋 他们到底想怎样
Those bastards. What do they want?
保罗探员 启动人质援救方案
Detective Paul, initiate hostage protocol.
给他们送通讯工具
Send them the comm.
Send them the comm!
让遥控飞机升空 我们必须和他们谈判
Get that drone in the air. We've got to start negotiating.
通讯工具到了
Comm's here.
你是谁
What's your name?
马尔多纳多队长
Captain Maldonado.
你怎么称呼
And you are?
我可以告诉你 不过我不想让你的努力白白浪费
Well, I'd tell you, but I don't want to nullify your efforts.
既然我们已经引起了你的注意
Now that we have your attention...
我们有几个要求
we have some demands.
佩吉 你可以把电话举起来让我听听他们在说什么吗
Paige, can you hold the phone up so I can hear what's going on?
我真的不想再把人质扔出去了
I really hate to throw out any more hostages.
我们就有话直说吧 如何
Let's get down to brass tacks, huh?
你想怎么样
What do you want?
第一
First,
让你的狙击手从屋顶撤离
get your snipers off the roof,
然后告诉那些集合在楼下待命的人
and tell those men you have assembled out front to stand down,
让他们远离这座大厦
and keep them away from the building,
否则还会有人质从天而降
or hostages will continue to fall from the sky.
告诉保罗探员让他的人撤离
Tell Detective Paul to have his men stand down.
B队 撤退
Bravo team, stand down.
都走了
All clear.
好了
Done.
还有什么
What else?
我们要三架垂直起降飞机在屋顶待命
We'd like three v-tols on the roof standing by,
确保我们安全到达边境
clear airspace from here to the border,
最后 我要一个裂变触发器
and finally, I'd like one fission igniter delivered to me, please.
那是军用武器
That's military-grade technology.
我无权支配
I don't have that authority.
那我建议你联系有这个权限的人
Well, then I suggest you contact someone who does.
面部识别成功
Facial recognition identified.
你现在听我说 卢卡斯
Now, you listen to me, Lucas,
如果你想让我跟你合作
if you want me to cooperate with you,
那么你也要配合我
I need you to cooperate with me.
你手上有多少人质
How many hostages do you have?
多到如果他们死了 你的饭碗就保不住了
More than enough to end your career if they die.
你还有四十三分钟
You have 43 minutes.
定时器设为四十三分钟 让鲁迪・洛姆来见我
Set the timer for 43 minutes, and get me Rudy Lom.
喂
Hello?
你还在吗
Are you there?
我在 佩吉
Right here, Paige.
有人来救我们吗
Is anyone coming?
你要撑住
You just hang tight.
我们马上就去救你
We're gonna be with you real soon.
你听到他们的对话了吗
Did you hear the phone call?
是的 我听到了 谢谢你
Yeah, I did. Thank you.
不要挂断 我马上回来
Just hold on a second. I'll be right back.
裂变触发器真有我想的那么危险吗
Is a fission igniter as bad as I think it is?
这是一个大型爆炸装置的触发系统
It's a trigger mechanism for a large explosive device.
百万吨级别
Megaton level.
百万吨
Megaton.
佩吉 你在吗
Paige, you there?
你能告诉我他们手上有多少人质吗
Can you tell me how many hostages they've got up there?
二十五个左右
25 or so.
至少在这个房间是这样
At least in this room.
我看不太清楚
It's hard for me to see.
你做得很好 佩吉
You're doing great, Paige.
你妹妹怎么样
How's your sister?
都是我的错
This is all my fault.
要不是我她就不会在这
She wouldn't be here if it wasn't for me.
她从镇子上来
She's visiting from out of town.
只是路过这里 想和我吃午饭
She just stopped by to have lunch...
可现在她却要独自面对这些
and now she's all alone.
佩吉 你能告诉我有多少持枪的人吗
Paige, can you tell me how many gunmen there are?
他们一直走来走去 我不知道
People keep coming and going; I don't know.
至少...五六个
Five... six, at least.
但应该更多
But there were more.
对不起 我做不到
I'm sorry, I can't do this.
我太害怕了
I'm so scared.
佩吉 你以前冰钓过么
Paige, you ever been ice fishing?
没
No.
我十一岁的时候
When I was 11 years old,
我爸带我去麦克法兰湖冰钓
my dad took me ice fishing to Lake McFarland.
准备回家的时候 突然间
We were coming back, and all of a sudden
冰面裂开了 我正好掉进去
the ice cracked, and I went right under.
我看不见 也无法呼吸
I couldn't see, I couldn't breathe.
我以为我就要死了
I thought I was gonna die.
湖水非常冷 像无数根针在扎我的全身一样
The water was so cold, it was like thousands of needles stinging every part of my body.
就在那时我爸跳了下来
And then my dad jumped in,
他抓住我 把我往岸上拖
and he grabbed me and started dragging me back to shore.
你想让她睡着么
Are you trying to put her to sleep?
即使我们还没脱离危险
And even though we were still in a lot of danger,
我却感觉很安全
I felt safe.
我觉得
I felt like...
一切都会好的
everything was gonna be okay,
因为我不是一个人
because I wasn't alone.
佩吉
Paige...
你不是孤身一人
you're not alone.
我会陪着你
I'm with you.
一切都会没事的
Everything is gonna be okay.
你相信我么
Do you believe me?
我相信
Yeah, I do.
很好 好姑娘
All right, good girl.
你要坚持下去
You just hang in there.
保罗
Yeah. Paul.
肯尼思和多利安有什么消息么
Any sign of Kennex and Dorian?
目前还没有
Uh, nothing so far.
让你的人留在原地
Keep your men back,
在每扇窗户和每个出口 布置好遥控飞机和侧位仪
but I want drones and spotters on every window and exit.
我要知道我的人现在怎么样了
I want to know what's happening with my men.
好的 没问题 长官
Yeah, you got it, Captain.
我不可能拿到裂变触发器
There's no way I can get a fission igniter.
如果有种方法能在给足他们要求的同时
What if there was a way to give them what they wanted
还能拖住他们呢
and stall them at the same time?
你有什么主意
What have you got?
我可以做一个假的
I could build a replica.
万一他们认出来了呢
What if they can spot a fake?
我做的可以通过扫描
I can make one that will pass a scan.
但如果他们检查出来了 或者直接就用了
If they test it out or try and use it immediately,
那我们就都完了
then we're out of luck.
我们可以冒这个险
That's risk we'll have to take.
我们开始吧
Let's get started.
- 长官 - 怎么了
- Captain?  - Yep?
卢卡斯・文森特是神圣开拓军队的高级特务
Lucas Vincent... he's a high-level operative in the Holy Reclamation Army,
那是一个分散式的恐怖组织
a decentralized network of terrorist cells
具有反西方倾向 有劫持人质的记录
with anti-Western bias and a history of hostage taking,
没有人质有好下场
none of them ending well.
去年八月他们劫持了东京附近的大使馆
Last August they took over an embassy near Tokyo.
使用相同的手段 强行闯入
Same MO... they enter with force,
引起媒体和执法机关的注意
drew the attention of the media and law enforcement
通过挟持人质达到他们的目的
using human hostages as collateral for their demands.
然后呢
What happened?
他们帮助他们的人逃出了监狱
They facilitated the release of several of their comrades.
只要得到他们想要的 他们就会放人
Once they got what they wanted, they released the hostages.
但是他们不害怕杀人
But they're not afraid to take lives...
包括自己的命
including their own.
你知道么 每个人都会被楼梯绊倒
You know, everyone trips on stairs,
经统计大概每上2222个阶梯就发生一回
and it's calculated to occur in one in every 2,222 occasions.
真有趣
That's very interesting.
- 你知道什么才是更有趣的么 约翰 - 什么
- You know what would be interesting, John? - What?
就是你再给我讲一遍冰钓的故事
If you told me that ice fishing story again.
如果你想保持身材 我们可以每周末都去做越障训练
If you want to get in shape, we can run the O-course every weekend.
喔 真的能么
O-can we?
分头行动
Let's split up.
多利安 你还好么
Dorian, you okay?
约翰 快过来
John, get over here.
这层没人了
Floor's clear.
你还好么
You okay?
你脑袋破了
You took one to the head.
没错 被弹回来的子弹打到了
Yeah, ricochet.
你找到什么了
Whatcha got?
我也不确定
I'm not sure.
但是这上写了字
But there's writing on it.
"开始"
"Start."
- 开始 - 开始
- Start? - Start.
你查出他的身份了么
You I.D.'d him?
他叫迈克尔・多纳瑞
His name is Michael Demerais.
他是神圣开拓军队的一员
He's a member of the Holy Reclamation Army.
这就是幕后黑手
So they're behind this.
也许不是
Maybe not.
这是个变脸器
It's a facemaker.
所以 这人是谁
So who's this guy?
他叫格雷戈・斯通
His name is Gregor Stone.
他有持枪抢劫的案底
He has a few priors for armed robbery.
他们为什么要装成激进组织的成员
Why would they impersonate members of a radical organization?
怎么了
What's wrong?
我的动态电压调节被子弹摧毁了
My dynamic voltage scaling has been damaged by the bullet.
你能说的简单一点么
You want to say that a little less complicated?
五分钟后我将不能走路
I won't be able to walk in five minutes.
我们的飞机呢
Where are our v-tols?
我正在努力
I'm working on it.
根据它发出的信号的频率
Based on the frequency at which these transmit...
我测出这楼里有七个变脸人
I detect seven facemakers in the building.
如果想隐藏他们的身份
If they hide their identities,
带个面具不是更方便
why not just wear a mask?
为什么要伪装成别人
Why pretend to be something else?
这个问题问的好
That's a good question.
好了
All right.
让我来试试修修你
Let's try and fix you.
伤口看起来怎么样
How does it look?
没什么大碍
Yeah, it's, uh, totally fine.
几乎都看不到它
You can hardly see it.
好吧
Okay.
那我要怎么做
So, what do I do?
有一条品红色的肌腱
All right, there's a magenta colored tendon.
我需要你切掉它
I need you to cut it.
等下 这...这东西干净吗
All right, is... is that thing clean?
当然干净
Of course it is.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
确定
Positive.
该死
Damn it.
- 我说的是品红色 - 它是品红色的
- I said magenta. - It was magenta.
- 我说的是品红色 那是淡紫色 - 该死的品红
- I said magenta. That was lavender. - The hell's magenta?
这里面有五十种色调的紫色
There's 50 shades of purple in there.
我告诉你了 那是条淡紫色的
I'm telling you, that was the lavender one.
- 不 不 好了 等一下 - 怎么了
- No, no. Okay, wait a minute. - What?
- 你拿着这东西干嘛 - 切点电线啊
- What are you doing with that? - Gotta cut the wire.
这东西不能进入我的脑袋
That's not going inside of my head.
- 我是你的搭档 相信我 - 如果鲁迪在这
- I'm your partner, trust me. - If Rudy were here,
他肯定对你有很大的意见
he'd have a really big issue with you right now.
- 约翰... - 有些情况比这还糟糕
- John... - Look, it could always be worse.
- 约翰 统计... - 你会没事的
- John, the statistics... - You're going to be fine.
多利安
Dorian?
请别这样看着我
Please stop looking at me like that.
离你交付假的裂变装置还有五分钟
You have five minutes to deliver the decoy fission device.
我已经尽快在做了
I'm working as fast as I can.
四分四十五秒
Four minutes, 45 seconds.
完美是不能计时的
You can't put a clock on perfection.
很明显 设计你的礼仪芯片的人当时很仓促
Clearly someone was rushing when they designed your manners chip.
约翰 你还在吗
John, are you there?
我可以听到你 佩吉
I can hear you, Paige.
他们移动了
They've moved.
他们老去拐角的窗户
They keep going to a corner window...
做些什么
doing something.
他们在做什么
What are they doing?
我不知道
I don't know.
我妹妹...她在哭
My sister... she's crying.
其中一个看守 他总在看她
And one of the guards, he keeps looking at her.
佩吉 我保证我马上就去救你
Look, I promise I'll get to you soon, Paige.
你妹妹叫什么名字
What's your sister's name?
詹娜
Jenna.
Jenna?
她的中间名是格特鲁德
Her middle name's Gertrude.
这名字够汉子
Ooh, that's rough.
Gertrude这个名字的含义是"军队的力量"
你的中名叫什么
What's yours?
不 不 不 我不告诉你
Oh, no. No, no, we're not doing that.
快点 告诉我
Come on, tell me.
好吧 但你最好不要告诉别人 好吗
All right, but you better not tell anyone, okay?
这是警察的命令
Police orders.
雷金纳德
It's Reginald.
我爸是艾尔顿・约翰的脑残粉
My dad was a big Elton John fan.
谁
Who?
艾尔顿・约翰 他是过去的一名歌手
Elton John. He's an old-time singer.
据说 他的真名是雷金纳德
Apparently, his real name was Reginald.
你还好吧
You okay?
真恶心
Gross.
但还好
But good.
有情况
Something's happening.
过来帮忙
Get over here and help.
其中一个枪手
One of the gunmen,
他受伤了
he's hurt.
谁打伤的你
Who shot you?
有两个男人在这楼里
There are two men in the building.
是条子吗
Cops?
我不知道
I don't know.
格雷戈在哪
Where's Gregor?
我们走散了
We got separated.
你想让我们去找他吗
Do you want us to look for him?
不
No.
调更多的人去楼梯间
Put more men on the stairwell.
不让任何人上这层楼
No one gets up on this floor.
去 你 去
Go. You, go.
约翰 他们知道你在这楼里
John, they know you're in the building.
他们派了几个拿着枪的人去守着楼梯
They sent a couple guys with giant guns to guard the stairs.
就算你上来了
Even if you do get up here,
你怎么进的来呢
how are you gonna get in?
相信我 佩吉
Trust me, Paige.
我们会找到路来救你的
We'll find a way to get to you.
我对你很失望啊 马尔多纳多队长
I'm disappointed in you, Captain Maldonado.
我还以为我们处的很好
I thought we were getting along so well.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
我说撤掉条子
I said no cops.
我已经召回了我的人
I pulled my men back.
我的人都在大楼外面 疏散人群
The only people I have there are conducting the evacuation, outside the building.
那你怎么解释我的人刚在楼下杀了两个警察
Then how do you explain the two cops my men just killed downstairs?
他在唬人
He's bluffing.
我不知道你杀了什么人
I don't know what men you killed,
但他们不是我的人
but they weren't mine.
我们有约在先
We made a deal.
我给你想要的条件 没有人会死
I get you what you want, no one else dies.
我什么时候能拿到我的裂变触发器
When do I get my fission ignitor?
已经在路上了 十分钟以内到
It's on its way, ten minutes or less.
很好 多一分钟你就会在人行道上多看到一具尸体
Great. Every minute longer is another body you'll be scraping off the pavement.
闭上你的嘴
Keep your mouth shut.
约翰
John?
我要出去
I'm going out there.
我不能让詹娜一个人面对
I can't leave Jenna alone.
佩吉 那是个不明智的做法
Paige, that's a bad idea.
我必须那么做
I have to. I have to.
我们再有几层楼就到了
We're a few floors away.
她需要我
She needs me.
我需要她
I need her.
如果我们会死...我也要和她在一起
If we're gonna die... ...I want to be with her.
她是我妹妹
She's my sister.
现在是我唯一可以混进人群里的机会
Now is my only chance to blend in
而他们不会发现我
without anyone seeing me.
佩吉 呆在那别动
Paige, just stay where you are.
我会开着机
I'll leave my phone open.
你会听到我们的对话
You'll be able to hear what's going on.
佩吉 太冒险了
Paige, it's too risky.
听着 别动
Listen to me, just stay put.
我必须这样做
I have to.
- 我必须这样做 - 佩吉 拜托了
- I have to. - Paige, please,
佩吉 听我的 佩吉
just listen to me. Paige.
佩吉 你在听吗 佩吉
Paige, are you there? Paige?
我在
I'm here.
没事的
It'll be okay.
保罗探员
Detective Paul?
收到 触发器已经可以传送
Copy. The ignitor is ready for delivery.
快点
Come on.
快 快 速度
Come on, come on, speed it up.
长官 准备好了
It's good to go, sir.
好 听你命令
Okay, waiting on your order.
传送
Send it.
送她上去
Let's get her up.
舆洗室
打扰一下
Excuse me.
我要去下洗手间
I have to go to the bathroom.
你想要我尿在地上 是么
You're not going to make me pee on the floor, are you?
给你三十秒
You've got 30 seconds.
嗨 老大
Hey, boss...
又有东西送上来了
we're getting another delivery.
遥控飞机到了
The drone's coming.
通话中
卢卡斯 我们有约在先
We had an agreement, Lucas.
我们真诚地给了你想要的东西
We've operated in good faith here.
我相信你做到了
I believe in honoring a deal.
准备
Stand by.
等我们放了人质我会通知你的
I'll let you know how we're gonna release the hostages.
希望能骗过他们
Let's hope they buy it.
现在把这个消息发给其他人
Send the message to the other crew now.
他们应该准备好了
They should be ready.
是时候结束这场战争了
It's time to wind this up.
什么其他人
What other crew?
或许还有更多他们的人在这栋楼里
Maybe there are more of them in the building.
- 或许他们在楼外面 - 但干扰器还开着
- Maybe they're outside the building. - But the jammer's still on.
除非他们有人在外面 不然他们不可能和别人通话
If they have people outside, they wouldn't be able to talk to each other.
除非他们用别的通话方式
Unless they were talking some other way.
开始
"Start."
他们肯定是用它来和某人近距离的在大楼里进行
They must be using it as some sort of point-to-point communication
某种点对点的通讯
with someone in proximity of the building.
佩吉说那个头目
Paige said the man in charge...
一直走到窗边
kept going to the window.
我没想到他们能搞来这个
I didn't think they'd come through.
如果这是追踪装置呢
What if there's a tracking device?
反正我们不带走它
We're not taking it anyway.
没关系
It doesn't matter.
他不想要那个装置 说不通啊
He doesn't want the tech. That doesn't make sense.
为什么挟持人质然后和我们要一个不想带走的装置
Why take hostages and negotiate for tech you don't want?
或许这是调虎离山
Maybe it's a diversion.
对啊 但为了什么
Yeah, but for what?
在临近建筑物里有什么
Are there any targets
更有价值的目标是他们想要的么
of value in the adjacent buildings?
唯一有价值的目标就是
The only target of any value is
专门研究钯的重金属称重站了
a precious metal weigh station specializing in palladium.
他们想抢劫
It's a heist.
钯 那就值得他们做这么多了
Palladium. That would make all this worthwhile.
包起来
Wrap it up.
我们只有十分钟
We're out of here in ten.
丹尼尔 坚持住
Hang in there, Daniel.
当这结束后 我们就已经在某处的海滩上了
When this is over, we'll all be on a beach somewhere,
你也会完好如初的
you'll be as good as new.
我需要医生
I need a doctor.
马上就有
Soon.
那个哔哔声是什么
What's that beeping?
你和其他人带上三个人质
You and the guys pick three hostages.
为什么
Why?
以防万一
We may need insurance.
收好东西
Let's pack it up.
约翰 他们激活了一个光弹
John, they've activated a light bomb.
他们想要灭口
They're gonna kill the hostages.
- 你要干嘛 - 按原计划 我们上楼
- What are you doing? - Sticking to the plan. We're going up.
约翰 他们知道我们在这
John, they know we're here.
他们也会料到我们会上楼
They're expecting us to come up the stairs.
我们不可能活着走到二十五楼的
We won't make it to the 25th floor alive.
他说的你也都听到了
You heard him.
我们没有其他选择
We have no choice.
是我没得选择
I don't have a choice.
人质命悬一线
People's lives are in jeopardy.
你中枪了 脑子里又塞了口香糖
You've been shot. Your head's full of bubble gum.
你不能一个人去冒险
You can't do this alone.
我必须去
I have to.
那我跟你去
Then I'm coming with you.
你不能去
You can't.
我被设计来做这些的 约翰
I'm designed to do this, John.
时间到了
It's time.
詹娜
Jenna...
何不能跟我一起来呢
why don't you come with me.
不要 不准碰她
No, no, no. Don't you touch her.
别碰她 把我带走吧
Don't you touch her. Take me!
放她走 不然我干掉你
Let her go! I will shoot you!
不 把我带走吧 不 放开那女孩
No, no! Take me! No, leave her!
把我带走吧 拜托了
Take me! Please! Me!
警察 快趴下
Police! Get down!
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
我从来不杀我不认识的人
I've never killed a man I didn't know.
但是
But then again...
你不是人类
you're not a man.
不是吗
Are you?
你终于出现了 格雷戈
Nice of you to show up, Gregor.
你到底去哪了
Where the hell have you been?
我们以为你挂了
We thought you were dead.
马尔多纳多
Maldonado?
- 约翰 - 人质安全了
- John? - The hostages are secure.
他们是来抢钯的
The whole thing is a palladium heist.
把它关掉 就现在
Shut it off... now!
他们利用我们关闭了整个警报系统
They got us to block the alarm system.
把干扰器关掉
Turn the jammer off!
保罗探员 马上把干扰器关掉
Detective Paul, turn off the jammer now!
关掉它
Shut it off.
走吧
Let's go.
谢啦
Thank you.
约翰
John?
你一定是佩吉
You must be Paige.
谢谢
Thank you.
没呢 谢谢你
No. Thank you.
你很勇敢
You were very brave.
你今天帮忙救了不少人
You helped save a lot of lives today.
你的搭档在哪呢
Where's your partner?
他在...
Oh, he's, uh...
他在进行修补
he's getting patched up.
约翰 这是我妹妹
John, this is my sister.
这是詹娜
This is Jenna.
詹娜 很高兴认识你
Jenna, it's a pleasure to meet you.
我听了很多关于你的故事
I've heard a lot about you.
你没事太好啦
I'm glad you're okay.
谢啦
Thanks.
我得到一些有关犯人的情报
I've got some intel on the perps.
这一切的幕后黑手是杰拉德・雷顿
Guy behind it all was Gerald Leighton.
他和他的团伙跟过去两年四起大型抢劫案都有关系
We linked him and his men to four high-value robberies in the last two years.
他们用警方的干扰器来抢劫钯
Using police jamming protocol to initiate a palladium heist.
这群贼可够聪明的
Pretty elaborate for a bunch of thieves.
要搞定这些文书工作可麻烦了
It's going to be a paperwork nightmare.
我还以为你过来是感谢我呢
And I thought you had come down here to thank me.
为什么 因为你履行了你的职责
For what? Doing your job?
申明一下
Just for the record,
我可是提醒过你从那栋楼里出来 对吧
I did tell you to get out of the building, right?
我发誓 我什么也没听到
I swear, all I heard was static.
我要跟你商量个事呢 警探
Oi! I've got a bone to pick with you, Detective.
口香糖 真的假的
Chewing gum? Really?
你能用口香糖修好赛车吗
Would you fix a race car with chewing gum?
是啊 如果它坏了而我还得赢下比赛
Uh, yeah, if it was busted, and I need to win a race.
他需要做个全面检查
He'll need extensive diagnostics.
这个不着急
Ah, that can wait.
来吧 我们去吃面
Come on, let's go get some noodles.
你应该明白我不吃东西
You are aware that I don't eat.
太好了 我买单 走吧
Perfect. I'm buying. Let's roll.
那我就在这等吧 怎么样
Well, I'll just wait here, shall I?
谢谢你回来救我
Thank you for what you did back there.
别客气
Don't mention it.
再说 没人可以动我的咖啡加热机
Besides, no one messes with my coffee warmer.
嘿 约翰 你还记得你跟佩吉说的那个故事
Hey, John, you know that story you told Paige,
你小时候掉到冰湖里去的那个
when you fell through the ice as a kid?
当有枪指在我头上的时候 我有相同的感觉
When that gun was pointed at my head, I felt something similar.
我不想死
I-I didn't want to die.
我知道死对于我来说不一样 但是...
I know it's not the same with me, but...
嘿 死了就死了
Hey, dead is dead.
是啊
Yeah.
我想也是
I suppose so.
为什么不放点歌听呢
Why don't you chuck some music on?
艾尔顿・约翰
Eldon John, hah?
你都听到了 对不
You heard it, didn't you?
本尼和乐队
Buh-buh-buh Bennie and the Jets
Bennie and the Jets
别唱了 拜托
Don't. Don't. Please, don't do that.
说什么都没用 雷金纳德
Whatever you say, Reginald.
本尼
Bennie
本尼 本尼和乐队
Bennie, Bennie and the Jets...
卢卡斯 文森特
神圣开拓军队
识别芯片
身份识别
所属组织
神圣开拓军队
身份识别
结果: 格雷戈 斯通
迪特尔贵金属公司 新月街
十分钟
扫描声波
探测到光弹
识别装置
爆炸性物质/光弹
状态: 已激活
身份识别